Stanley L. Aiges Papers 7058
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Stanley L. Aiges Papers
1973-2019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Aiges, Stanley Leonard, 1921-
7058
10 cubic feet. 10 RCs
Binders containing written decisions made by Stanley L. Aiges, ILR Alum '58 and recipient of the 1985 Groat Award, over the course of his 50 year career as a self-employed arbitrator.
15645095
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the written decisions for cases before independent arbitrator Stanley L. Aiges. The decisions are arranged chronologically, and a guide to all cases may be found in Box 1, Folder 1 "Case Index, 1973 - 2019." Additionally, a series of decisions concerning Mack Trucks, Inc. are foldered seperately in chronological order.
Biographical / Historical
Stanley L. Aiges is a labor-management arbitrator who lives and practices in Fort Lee, NJ. Mr. Aiges graduated from the ILR School, Cornell University in 1958. Mr. Aiges was awarded the Judge William B. Groat Alumni Award in 1985 in recognition of his contributions to the field of arbitration.
Arbitration, Industrial; Labor disputes; Papers (documents)
15645095
- Case Index, 1973-2019 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Index of cases in collection, arranged chronologically, with identifying numbers and subject areas
- Annotated Loose Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Decisions, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  Cases 73-01 through 73-17, 74-01 through 74-15, 74-17 through 74-20, 74-46
- Arbitration Decisions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  Cases 75-01 through 75-07, 75-09 through 75-34, 75-36 through 75-50
- Arbitration Decisions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  Cases 75-51 through 75-61, 75-63 through 75-80, 75-82 through 75-89
- Arbitration Decisions, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  Cases 76-01 through 76-23, 76-26 through 76-46, 76-48 through 76-60
- Arbitration Decisions, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
  Cases 76-61 through 76-95, 76-98 through 76-111, 76-113 through 76-116
- Arbitration Decisions, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
  Cases 77-01 through 77-50
- Arbitration Decisions, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  Cases 77-51 through 77-100
- Arbitration Decisions, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  Cases 78-01 through 78-37, 78-39 through 78-50
- Arbitration Decisions, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
  Cases 78-51 through 78-88, 78-90 through 78-95
- Arbitration Decisions, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  Cases 79-01 through 79-36, 79-38 through 79-39, 79-41 through 79-50
- Arbitration Decisions, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  Cases 79-51 through 79-77, 79-77 through 79-90
- Mack Trucks, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12-14)
  Cases involving Mack Trucks, Inc. plants - Hagerstown, Allentown, Macungie, Hayward Division, and Bridgewater Parts Depot
- Arbitration Decisions, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15-17)
  Cases 80-01 through 80-02, 80-04 through 80-39, 80-41, 80-43 through 80-45, 80-47 through 80-50
- Arbitration Decisions, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  Cases 80-51 through 80-99
- Arbitration Decisions, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  Cases 81-01 through 81-48, 81-50
- Arbitration Decisions, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  Cases 81-51 through 81-52, 81-54, 81-56 through 81-76, 82-01 through 82-06, 82-08, 82-10 through 82-12, 82-14 through 82-20
- Arbitration Decisions, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9-11)
  Cases 82-01 through 82-06, 82-08, 82-10 through 82-12, 82-14 through 82-24, 82-26 through 82-50
- Arbitration Decisions, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Cases 82-51 through 82-60, 82-63 through 82-71
- Arbitration Decisions, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13-15)
  Cases 83-01 through 83-13, 83-15 through 83-19, 83-21 through 83-25, 83-27, 83-30, 83-32 though 83-36, 83-39 through 83-40, 83-42 through 83-46, 83-49 through 83-57
- Arbitration Decisions, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
  Cases 84-01 through 84-50
- Arbitration Decisions, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Cases 84-51 through 84-70
- Arbitration Decisions, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  Cases 85-01 through 85-06, 85-08 through 85-27, 85-29, 85-31 through 85-32, 85-34 through 85-35, 85-39
- Arbitration Decisions, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
  Cases 85-40 through 85-44, 85-46 through 85-69
- Arbitration Decisions, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6-8)
  Cases 86-01 through 86-12, 86-14 through 86-20, 86-22 through 86-40
- Arbitration Decisions, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9-12)
  Cases 86-41 through 86-43, 86-45, 86-47 through 86-63, 86-65, 86-67 through 86-78, 86-80 through 86-83
- Arbitration Decisions, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13-16)
  Cases 87-01 through 87-09, 87-11 through 87-14, 87-16 through 87-39
- Arbitration Decisions, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 17-20)
  Cases 87-41 through 87-58, 87-60 through 87-81
- Arbitration Decisions, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  Cases 88-01 through 88-35
- Arbitration Decisions, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
  Cases 88-36 through 88-52, 88-54 through 88-70
- Arbitration Decisions, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7-9)
  Cases 89-01 through 89-18, 89-20 through 89-26, 89-28 through 89-35
- Arbitration Decisions, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10-12)
  Cases 89-36 through 89-52, 89-54 through 89-65
- Arbitration Decisions v.I, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13-15)
  Cases 90-01 through 90-30
- Arbitration Decisions v.II, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
  Cases 90-31 through 90-63
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 19-20)
  Cases 91-01 through 91-30
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21-22)
  Cases 91-31 through 91-53, 91-55 through 91-63
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  Cases 92-01 through 92-17, 92-18 through 92-34
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
  Cases 92-35 through 92-67
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5-7)
  Cases 93-01 through 93-15, 93-17 through 93-18, 93-20 through 93-29, 93-31 through 93-40
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
  Cases 93-41 through 93-52, 93-54 through 93-76
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
  Cases 94-01 through 94-18, 94-21 through 94-30
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
  Cases 94-31 through 94-50, 94-52 through 94-57
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  Cases 95-01 through 95-33
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  Cases 95-34 through 95-67
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  Cases 96-01 through 96-29
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
  Cases 96-30 through 96-55
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
  Cases 97-01 through 97-30
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
  Cases 97-31 through 97-38, 97-40 through 97-53
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
  Cases 98-01 through 98-29
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
  Cases 98-30 through 98-58
- Arbitration Decisions v. I, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
  Cases 99-01 through 99-25
- Arbitration Decisions v. II, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
  Cases 99-26 through 99-49
- Arbitration Decisions, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  Cases 00-01 through 00-51
- Arbitration Decisions, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4-6)
  Cases 01-01 through 01-45
- Arbitration Decisions, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
  Cases 02-01 through 02-41
- Arbitration Decisions, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 10-12)
  Cases 03-01 through 03-05, 03-07 through 03-42
- Arbitration Decisions, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 13-15)
  Cases 04-01 through 04-37
- Arbitration Decisions, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  Cases 05-01 through 05-19, 05-21 through 05-37
- Arbitration Decisions, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
  Cases 06-01 through 06-32
- Arbitration Decisions, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 7-9)
  Cases 07-01, 07-03 through 07-31, 07-35 through 07-37
- Arbitration Decisions, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 10-12)
  Cases 08-01 through 08-34
- Arbitration Decisions, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
  Cases 09-01 through 09-36
- Arbitration Decisions, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  Cases 10-01 through 10-12, 10-14 through 10-28
- Arbitration Decisions, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
  Cases 11-01 through 11-34
- Arbitration Decisions, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  Cases 12-01 through 12-25
- Arbitration Decisions, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 3-5)
  Cases 13-01 through 13-19, 13-21, 13-23 through 13-27
- Arbitration Decisions, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  Cases 14-01 through 14-22
- Arbitration Decisions, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  Cases 15-01 through 15-06, 15-08 through 15-22
- Arbitration Decisions, 2016 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Cases 16-01 through 16-05, 16-07 through 16-17
- Arbitration Decisions, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Cases 17-01 through 17-18, 17-20 through 17-22
- Arbitration Decisions, 2018 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Cases 18-01 through 18-15
- Arbitration Decisions, 2019 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Cases 19-01 through 19-20